<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>nym on Merak.run</title>
    <link>https://merak.run/tags/nym/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nym on Merak.run</description>
    <image>
      <title>Merak.run</title>
      <url>https://merak.run/merak.svg</url>
      <link>https://merak.run/merak.svg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 10:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://merak.run/tags/nym/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to restake?</title>
      <link>https://merak.run/howtorestake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 10:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merak.run/howtorestake/</guid>
      <description>As you already know, staking allows you to get rewards by depositing your tokens on a validator.
Merak has restake support enabled, so it&amp;rsquo;s your turn to take profit of it!
First you need to delegate tokens to the validator in the traditional way, either via restake.app or via your preferred wallet.
If you&amp;rsquo;re using restake you&amp;rsquo;ll see a dialog similar to this: Once it&amp;rsquo;s done, if you visit the list of delegations, it will show that Auto-compounding requires to fix permissions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restake support</title>
      <link>https://merak.run/restake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 14:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merak.run/restake/</guid>
      <description>Merak has added restake support for the validator, you can find the current active links in the validator page.
In short, restake, via the link provided, allows you, as delegator to autocompound the earnings from staking for free.
You can click on the icons in the networks field in the profile tab to select the validator in other networks where restaking is supported by the validator.
How it works? Using AuthZ support in some chains, your wallet grants access to the validator to claim rewards in your name and delegate them again to the same validator, meaning that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to do that manually (and you don&amp;rsquo;t need to pay the fees for it, as those are paid by the validator itself).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Validator</title>
      <link>https://merak.run/validator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 22:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merak.run/validator/</guid>
      <description>Merak is a chain Validator on the following projects:
Mainnet Network 📈 Stake Status Description of project Nym Mainnet (Genesis) Nym : Infrastructure to prevent leaks on data and metadata Passage 3D Autocompound or Stake Mainnet (Genesis) Passage 3D is an accessible and customizable 3D world for video chat, presentations, collaboration and e-commerce. Sifchain Autocompound or stake Betanet Dex Testnets Network 📈 Stake Status Description of project Redbelly No longer participating We&amp;rsquo;ve stopped collaborating on those projects to focus or efforts on others based on different reasons</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nym validator</title>
      <link>https://merak.run/blog/nym-validator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 13:29:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merak.run/blog/nym-validator/</guid>
      <description>Merak is a Nym validator powering the network.
Check the network explorer for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nym Validator</title>
      <link>https://merak.run/nym/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 18:34:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merak.run/nym/</guid>
      <description>Visit at https://www.mintscan.io/nyx/validators/nvaloper18mgnd9k6rytn6tz7pf8d2d4dawl7e9crunrsxd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
